[Footsteps]
[REINER] Me? Only thing
I want is to go back home.
That's all I care about now.
[BERTHOLDT] I joined the ranks
hoping for assignment
to the Military Police.
Tucked away in the Interior.
What about you?
Why did you sign up?
Why'd I join?
I decided I have to kill them.
I won't stop
till every single Titan
is dead and rotting.
Dead. Every last one.
[REINER] You saw what those
monsters are capable of.
And you still
want to take them on?
I know you've
got what it takes.
I can see it in you.
Am I wrong here?
[Sniffs]
[EREN]
Damn you! You traitors!
[Roars]
♪ Opening Song
Eren!
[MIKASA]
What's wrong with me?
Why didn't I slice
their goddamn heads off?
That was the perfect chance.
Why did I hesitate? Why?
[MIKASA]
That was it.
There won't be
another opportunity.
Move! Everyone!
[SOLDIERS groan]
It's got Ymir!
[grunts] Oh, hell!
She's not the only one!
[KEIJI]
Shit!
[CHRISTA gasps]
No. This isn't happening!
How can Bertholdt...?
Soldiers! Prepare to attack!
The Colossal Titan
doesn't walk away from this!
It's a threat to all mankind!
Swarm and terminate!
[KEIJI]
Freak's as slow as they say.
[GOGGLES] Size is
all he has going for him.
[MALE SOLDIER 32F] Compared to
Titans we're usually up against,
this one's a piece of cake!
[MOBLIT]
Simple!
[HANGE] He's wide open!
Slice the nape!
[Yells]
[KEIJI]
What the hell?
[MALE SOLDIER 32F]
It's too hot!
Argh! All of you fall back!
My hand!
Water! We need water!
[Gasps]
He's vanishing!
I don't know.
Something's different here.
The last time he disappeared,
it was more or less
instantaneous.
He's maintaining
his form to emit heat.
I think he's
protecting himself.
As long as he generates
steam our rigs are useless!
What, what do we do?
Now? Nothing. Except wait.
Squads three and four take
position behind the target.
Rashad has command.
Got it!
[HANGE] Squad two, stay put.
Lauda has command.
[LAUDA]
Understood!
[HANGE] How long he
can act like a blast furnace
remains to be seen.
But he'll come
out of there eventually.
When he does,
we'll rush the big bastard.
Listen up.
I want you to forget about
taking them alive.
Destroy them.
No second thoughts.
You're with me.
Right, squad one, look alive!
We've got a date
with the Armored Titan!
Christa! Conny!
Move further back!
For now, just
take care of those two.
Ymir, she--
She's not dead.
It just isn't possible.
I know it. Please save her!
Don't worry.
[CONNY] Hang on! What about
Reiner and Bertholdt?
They're screwed! Neither one
of them has their ODM gear!
I'm begging you,
wherever they are,
bring them back!
[Gasps]
[EREN] Reiner.
You lying piece of shit.
Going off on what it means
to be a soldier.
Always talking about honor.
Played us all for fools, huh?
Combat training
must've been a joke to you.
How much were you holding back?
And here I took you
to be real stand-up guy.
Calm under pressure.
Intensely focused.
The sort of man who puts
his comrades before himself.
Damn you. I'd have
given anything in the world
to be half as strong as you.
You were my hero.
[MIKASA grunts]
[MIKASA]
That did nothing!
He barely flinched
when Eren hit him.
And my blades
don't even make a dent.
[Grunts]
He's not like Annie.
His armor's head to toe!
Eren!
[EREN]
Hey, Reiner. Asshole.
I don't know what kind of face
you're making right now...
...but I hope you
miserable pieces of shit
are pleased with yourselves.
I bet I could scour through
the history of mankind
and not find anyone
a fraction as evil.
[MIKASA grunting]
[EREN]
You should be erased.
Trash like you
can't be allowed to exist.
What was going
through your head?
You disgust me!
Just thinking about your face
makes my insides churn!
You make me want to puke!
You're a pest! A revolting,
oversized pest!
And pests have to
be exterminated!
[Groans]
Hey, take it easy!
That hurt!
We're just sparring.
You're supposed
to hold back a little.
If you want to hold back,
that's your business.
I defend myself
assuming you're coming at me
with everything you've got.
Otherwise, what's the point?
Let's remember
I'm the girl. I'm weaker.
I have to protect
my frail little body
from the big bad man.
What? Ha-ha, Annie.
Very funny. You're a riot.
Frail little nothin'.
I'm the one who just got
shoved in the dirt, you know.
Good point.
[ANNIE] That last move wasn't
about who's stronger, okay?
I was using a special
defense technique.
Comes in handy
when your opponent
has a few pounds on you.
Trust me. You could
benefit from learning it.
Sure, uh--
What do you say we take
a break for now, though?
[EREN groans]
[ANNIE grunts]
Right. That's enough, Annie.
You can let go.
Come on. I've barely
shown you how this works
and already you're surrendering?
There's a two-fold benefit here.
Or don't you want to learn
how to talk to women?
Fine! Whatever! Just
please stop strangling me!
Ah. So you are interested
in what I can show you.
[REINER groans]
[REINER and EREN groan]
Not really sure I wanna
know how you got here.
[MIKASA]
Hey, Annie.
Your technique seems
pretty solid.
Teach me.
[ANNIE]
I'm flattered, but...
...it's a method
for normal people.
So, why would  you ever need it?
Still, I'm curious to know
if it works on animals.
Let's find out.
This is happening? Oh crap.
Hold up! Are these two
actually about to fight?
This is gonna be epic!
--Who--? Who do we bet on?
--What d'you mean? Annie.
What? Idiot!
Dinner says Mikasa
wipes the floor with 'er!
[REINER] Which one of 'em
you think's gonna win?
Well, I...
How should I know?
[EREN]
Wait. How did that play out?
And why's it coming to me now?
Is this--? Is this my life
flashing before my eyes?
So what? Who gives a shit?
It's not like it matters.
Not when I feel like this.
No! Back down!
You can't win in a fistfight!
Make a break for the wall!
Eren, please! Don't be rash!
[EREN TITAN roars]
Eren!
Oh, no!
He's blinded by rage!
[ARMIN gasps]
[Gasps]
What the hell is he doing?
Wait, that-- Holy crap!
That's Annie's technique!
[EREN]
You know what?
There's no telling what
you murdering hypocrites
were trying to accomplish.
But now that I think about it,
your master plan seems
to have a few holes in it.
Wanna eradicate humanity?
Maybe next time don't teach me
how to kick your ass!
It's working!
I've got him locked!
There's still a chance!
[Grunts]
I don't think so!
[EREN TITAN roars]
[MIKASA]
Eren!
[EREN]
You're not going anywhere!
[EREN TITAN roars]
[Roars]
[Growls]
He did it!
[ARMIN] Eren!
Can you hear me? Run away!
You've got to get
closer to the wall!
They're trying to abduct you!
We can't let them do that!
Trust me. Escape is
our best option!
You say that,
but Armin, come on.
They're not just gonna
let us leave.
[REINER TITAN growls]
Both of you fall back! Now!
[Gasps]
[ALL groan]
[KEIJI]
Nice one, Eren! Good call!
Looks like he's
in control again.
Yeah, but Reiner's
not just gonna let him go.
You're right;
escape's impossible.
[Gasps]
What the hell?
[HANNES] The Colossal Titan.
I knew it!
Why'd he show up here
of all places?!
What's going on with Eren?
Where is he?
Uh. He and the others
are over that way!
[HANNES] What? So I take it
that's his Titan form, huh?
Listen up, Eren!
If we're going
to get you out of here,
you've got to
buy us some time.
Stop Reiner dead in his tracks!
Think you can manage
to break off his leg
with another one
of those joint holds?
Our blades don't
do much good against him.
He can't be outmuscled,
but he can be outsmarted
if you play it right.
[EREN TITAN]
Mhmm.
[Gasps]
Oooooo!
[ARMIN]
Mikasa! Take my blades.
I want you to use them.
I'm counting on you!
[EREN] This is the one time
where running away
guarantees victory.
You guys are screwed for
letting us see your true colors.
You've backed yourselves
into a corner.
[Gasps]
--What the--?
--He's fast!
[REINER TITAN growls]
[EREN] Shit! The leg!
Go for the leg!
Don't let Reiner
pin you! Get up!
Throw him!
[EREN grunts]
Dammit! There's too much
power behind his attack!
Since when is he
so light on his feet?
We're completely
and utterly useless!
No. It's not feasible
that his body is
as hard as stone
from head to toe.
He couldn't move as fast
if that were the case.
Warriors used to sheathe
themselves in armor.
Way back in the olden days.
They had to leave
certain sections uncovered
for freedom of movement, though;
like the armpits and groin
or the spot behind the knee.
[REINER TITAN grunts]
[EREN]
I can't dodge this.
[Grunts]
Well, if I'm
gonna get slammed...
Bring it!
There we go!
You're mine,
you son of a bitch!
[KEIJI]
Yeah! That's how it's done!
[EREN] Got him! Now it all
boils down to strength!
[EREN]
Damn it. I'm slipping!
[MIKASA yells]
[EREN]
Mikasa.
Nice cut!
[REINER TITAN groans]
[EREN] Try fighting back
minus a leg!
[EREN TITAN growls]
You've got this!
Go for it, Eren!
Rip the traitor's head off!
Drag him out into the open!
[EREN] I can win.
I can beat Reiner.
He's going down!
[REINER TITAN grunts]
[Growls]
Wha-- What's he--?
Heh. Good luck, pal.
You've got him! Keep it up!
[REINER TITAN growls]
[ARMIN]
What's he doing?
Why would he stop here?
[Roars]
[Gasps]
[REINER TITAN roars]
Everyone be on guard!
He's calling for backup!
No visual on
incoming Titans yet.
He ain't got a chance in hell.
Try screaming for help
without a head, asshole!
[MALE SOLDIER 32A]
It's almost off!
[CONNY]
Um, I don't like this.
Had to be some reason
for that scream.
[Squelching and cracking]
What the--?
No, no, no, no, no!
[REINER TITAN roars]
[Cracking]
[ALL Gasp]
[MALE SOLDIER 32A]
Above you! Look out!
[EREN Gasps]
♪ Closing Song ♪